https://www.elsb.com/privacy-policy/

Certificates of Deposit
Individual Retirement Accounts (IRA)
Mortgage Calculator
HomePersonal BankingBusiness BankingOnline BankingRatesAboutPromosLoansPrivacy PolicyDisclosuresSitemap
Click here to sign up and receive the LSB news and promos.
La Salle State BankLet's get to know each other.
Privacy Policy
As of 1/1/2017
FACTSWHAT DOES LaSALLE STATE BANK DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?FACTSWhy?WHAT DOES LaSALLE STATE BANK DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limwit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.FACTSWhat?WHAT DOES LaSALLE STATE BANK DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Account balances and transaction history
Credit history and credit scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.FACTSHow?WHAT DOES LaSALLE STATE BANK DO
WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons LaSalle State Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes LaSalle State Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?Reasons we can share your personal informationFor our everyday business purposes—such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausDoes LaSalle State Bank share?YesCan you limit this sharing?NoReasons we can share your personal informationFor our marketing purposes—to offer our products and services to youDoes LaSalle State Bank share?YesCan you limit this sharing?NoReasons we can share your personal informationFor joint marketing with other financial companiesDoes LaSalle State Bank share?NoCan you limit this sharing?We don't shareReasons we can share your personal informationFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiencesDoes LaSalle State Bank share?NoCan you limit this sharing?We don't shareReasons we can share your personal informationFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthinessDoes LaSalle State Bank share?NoCan you limit this sharing?We don't shareReasons we can share your personal informationFor our affiliates to market to youDoes LaSalle State Bank share?NoCan you limit this sharing?We don't shareReasons we can share your personal informationFor nonaffiliates to market to youDoes LaSalle State Bank share?NoCan you limit this sharing?We don't share
Questions?Call Customer Service at 815-223-8800
What we doWhat we doHow does LaSalle State Bank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We also restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide you products and services.What we doHow does LaSalle State Bank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or deposit money
Pay your bills or apply for a loan
Use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.What we doWhy can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
DefintionsDefintionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
LaSalle State Bank does not share with our affiliates.
DefintionsNonaffiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
LaSalle State Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
DefintionsJoint marketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
LaSalle State Bank doesn’t jointly market.
